[{"answer": "Well, I expect him to do well.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "I mean, the truth is Mitt Romney spent most of the first half of this year debating, so he should have the advantage, shouldn't he?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Are you setting the bar so low that we should now expect a fumble?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, I want change.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "I mean he must be exasperated, don't you think, that he's still in this thing?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Very well, thank you, Piers.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know how he does both.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "How does he do both?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, I -- you know, the last month hasn't been a very good one for the governor.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Ross, he's not suited to that role, apparently?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "I think -- I think this is a terrible strategy, actually, for the Romney campaign.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "What would you be zinging President Obama?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I love that Ross Douthat just called Mitt Romney Mr. Phony.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Final word from Charles?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Has it been demonized a bit, do you think?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I am who I am because of what I believe.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "How important has your faith been to you personally over the years?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "I guess I'm running for president now.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "To those who don't know anything about Mormonism or the Mormon Church, what are the biggest misconceptions?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Of course there are.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Are there misconceptions about the Mormon Church that annoy you?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Once, with the same guy.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "In your case twice with the same guy, right?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "It's properly in love.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "How's it going?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Better.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Better second time around?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "You worked each other out?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Should I be getting nervous?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, he is older.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Did you not try to get it Marie and Donny?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, that's the thing is we really didn't work together for like 28 years.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "What has it been like working with your brother on and off for so long?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Oh my gosh, we were laughing right before the show.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Just because you have basically done -- how many thousands of shows have you done yourself over the years, as a guest?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "I think you have to have an endless curiosity to do this.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "And people are fascinating, Piers, aren't they?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "They did?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Either that or you die young.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Do you think the great secret of show business, in the end, is longevity?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "I do a television show in L.A., and then I fly to Vegas and do the show there at night, then I get back on a plane and fly to L.A. for the show that day.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What do you do?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Yes, I'll make a bet with you on the Ryder Cup.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "As a European, do you fancy a bet?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "That was a collective you, all of you.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "It was a great party.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Do I take it the party was long and glorious?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Well, it was a tough couple of days.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "What was it about that meeting, that speech, which seemed to have turned the fortunes round the next day?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Jose was -- he was an amazing captain all week.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "He must have said something that really got you going?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "I think collectively as a team, we were playing in silence on the golf course.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Were you feeling the same way?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Even seeing them now, it really was one of the most remarkable comebacks I can think in any kind of sport.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "How good a feeling is it?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Yeah, that was it.", "docId": "121001pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Was the major driving factor -- let's be honest here -- the fact that you knew I had a 100 dollar bet with President Clinton?", "qSentId": 618}]